Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1
- Box: 34, Folder: 20 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Employment in 100 Cleveland Concerns/Industries, Publication (Box 34, Folder 20)
    By Committee on Labor Relations and Employment Managers Group (damaged). July 1930 - March 1932. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Employment in 100 Cleveland Concerns/Industries, Publication (Box 34, Folder 20)
    By The Employment Managers' Group. February 1943 - December 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Employment in 100 Cleveland Concerns/Industries, Publication (Box 34, Folder 20)
    By Cleveland Chamber of Commerce. June 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Employment in 100 Cleveland Concerns/Industries, Publication (Box 34, Folder 20)
    By Cleveland Chamber of Commerce. August 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Employment in 100 Cleveland Concerns/Industries, Publication (Box 34, Folder 20)
    By Cleveland Chamber of Commerce. April 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Employment in 100 Cleveland Concerns/Industries, Publication (Box 34, Folder 20)
    By Cleveland Chamber of Commerce. April 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Employment in 100 Cleveland Concerns/Industries, Publication (Box 34, Folder 20)
    By Cleveland Chamber of Commerce. January 1966 - October 1969. Item is in English.
- Box: 34, Folder: 21 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Business Bulletin, Publication (Box 34, Folder 21)
    By The Cleveland Trust Company. v.38:no.11 (1957: Nov. 11). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Business Bulletin, Publication (Box 34, Folder 21)
    By The Cleveland Trust Company. v.39:no.8 (1958:Aug. 16). Item is in English.
- Box: 34, Folder: 22 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Climax Molybdenum Company, Publication (Box 34, Folder 22)
    By Climax Molybdenum Company. First printing, 1973; Second Printing 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Working to keep pace with demand, Publication (Box 34, Folder 22)
    By Climax Molybdenum Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Five Minutes with Molybdenum, Publication (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Item 4: A Primer on Molybdenum in Life Processes, Publication (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Item 5: Henderson, Publication (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Item 6: Research at Climax Molybdenum, Publication (Box 34, Folder 22)
- Box: 34, Folder: 23 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Apprentice Training at Clinton Industries, Inc., Publication (Box 34, Folder 23)
    By P. E. Rider. 6-29-48. Item is in English.
- Box: 34, Folder: 24 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Decision of the Board of Arbitration March 14, 1911 and Rules and Plans of Procedure Adopted by the Board of Grievance, Publication (Box 34, Folder 24)
    By The Claok, Suit, and Skirt Manufacturers' Protective Association. March 14, 1911. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Conciliation, Arbitration and Sanitation in the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Industry in New York City, Publication (Box 34, Folder 24)
    By Bureau of Labor Department of Commerce and Labor. Protocol of September 2nd, 1910 and Its Workings. Reprint from Bulletin No. 98 Bureau of Labor Department of Commerce and Labor. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Association News, Publication (Box 34, Folder 24)
    By The Cloak, Suit, and Skirt Manufacturers' Protective Association for the Promotion of Mutuality and Efficiency. v.1:no.6 (1913:Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Conciliation, Arbitration, and Sanitation in the Cloak, Suit, and Skirt Industry in New York City, Publication (Box 34, Folder 24)
    By Department of Commerce and Labor Bureau of Labor. Part of Bulletin no.98 of the Bureau of Labor Statistics. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Agreement of July 16, 1924, Publication (Box 34, Folder 24)
    By Industrial Council of the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers' Protective Association with International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union and Joint Board of the Cloak, Skirt, Dress & Reefer Makers' Union of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Six Years' Work and Progress of the Joint Board of Sanitary Control in the Cloak, Suit and Skirt and the Dress and Waist Industries, Publication (Box 34, Folder 24)
    By Joint Board of Sanitary Control in the Cloak, Suit and Skirt and the Dress and Waist Industries. October 31st, 1910-October 31st, 1916. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Findings and Recommendations of the Council of Conciliation, Publication (Box 34, Folder 24)
    By Cloak, Suit and Skirt Industry. August 4, 1915. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Decisions of the Board of Arbitration in the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Industry, Publication (Box 34, Folder 24)
    By Board of Arbitration in the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Industry. January 21st, 1915 and February 5th and 6th, 1915. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Report of an Investigation by John Dickinson and Morris Kolchin With special reference to certain matters in controversy before the Commission, Publication (Box 34, Folder 24)
    By John Dickinson; Morris Kolchin. Item is in English.
- Box: 34, Folder: 25 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Clothing Industry of Rochester, Publication (Box 34, Folder 25)
    By Clothier's Exchange of Rochester, N. Y. June, 1891. Item is in English.
- Box: 34, Folder: 26 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Outline of a Labor Cost System in an Average Clothing Factory, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By The Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. May 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Inflation! Hickey Freeman Pays 71.6 center an Hour, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Fairchild Publications, Inc. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.995 (1962:Dec. 21). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.993 (1962:Dec. 7). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.989 (1962:Nov. 2). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.983 (1962:Sep. 21). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.976 (1962:Aug. 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.991 (1962:Nov. 23). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.990 (1962:Nov. 23). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.987 (1962:Nov. 19). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.988 (1962:Nov. 12). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.985 (1962:Oct. 26). Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.984 (1962:Sep. 21). Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.981 (1962:Aug. 29). Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.980 (1962:Aug. 29). Item is in English.
  - Item 16: We Met at the Waldorf: Interanational Convention of the Clothing Manufacturers Association, U.S.A., October 9th-10th-11th, 1950, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association, U.S.A. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Apparel Industry's Impact on New York City's Economy, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Lance I. Michaels. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.979 (1962:Aug. 17). Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.978 (1962:Aug. 10). Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.977 (1962:Aug. 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.975 (1962:July 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.974 (1962:July 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.973 (1962:July 20). Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.972 (1962:June 22). Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.968 (1962:May 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.967 (1962:May 11). Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.962 (1962:Mar. 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.955 (1962:Jan. 5). Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Statement Presented to the Federal Trade Commission, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. October 15, 1962. Item is in English.
- Box: 34, Folder: 27 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Training of Sewing Machinists--the Responsibilities of Management, Publication (Box 34, Folder 27)
    By Isabel Blain; C. A. Martin; J. Baker; Z. A. Young. Technological Report no 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Training of Sewing Machinists--the Responsibilities of Management, Publication (Box 34, Folder 27)
    By Isabel Blain; C. A. Martin; J. Baker; Z. A. Young. Technological Report no.5. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- Box: 35, Folder: 1 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.110 (1963:Apr. 12). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.? (1963:Mar. 29). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.103 (1963:Feb. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.? (1963:Jan. 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.999 (1963:Jan. 25). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.997 (1963:Jan. 7). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.996 (1963:Jan. 4). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.862 (1959:July 31). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.? (1959:Dec. 31). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.? (1959:Aug. 7). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.? (1959:Apr. 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.851 (1959:May 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.? (1957:Jan. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.? (1959:Mar. 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.694 (1956:Mar. 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.136 (1963:Dec. 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.135 (1963:Nov. 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.132 (1963:Nov. 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.128 (1963:Oct. 11). Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.129 (1963:Oct. 11). Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.133 (1963:Nov. 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.126 (1963:Sep. 26). Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.122 (1963:Aug. 14). Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.124 (1963:Aug. 28). Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.120 (1963:July 19). Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.119 (1963:July 12). Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.116 (1963:June 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.114 (1963:May 27). Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.115 (1963:May 22). Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.113 (1963:May 10). Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.109 (1963:Apr. 12). Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.? (1955:Dec. 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.? (1955:May 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.? (1954:May 16). Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.? (1957:Mar. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.? (1957:June 28). Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.? (1957:July 19). Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.? (1957:July 26). Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By report of Mill Relations Committee. no.? (1957:Aug. 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.? (1957:Sep. 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.768 (1957:Aug. 14). Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.? (1957:Aug. 23). Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.773 (1957:Sep. 11). Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.? (1957:Sep. 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 46: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.? (1957:Oct. 4). Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.? (1957:Oct. 11). Item is in English.
  - Item 48: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.? (1957:Oct. 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 49: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.? (1957:Oct. 25). Item is in English.
  - Item 50: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.? (1957:Nov. 11). Item is in English.
  - Item 51: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.? (1957:Dec. 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 52: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.? (1957:Dec. 27). Item is in English.
  - Item 53: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.? (1958:Jan. 10). Item is in English.
  - Item 54: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Assiociation Of The U.S.A. no.? (1958:Jan. 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 55: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.? (1958:Mar. 7). Item is in English.
  - Item 56: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.? (1958:Apr. 4). Item is in English.
  - Item 57: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.? (1958:Mar. 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 58: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.? (1958:May 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 59: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.809 (1958:May 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 60: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.? (1958:May 2). Item is in English.
  - Item 61: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.? (1958:May 16). Item is in English.
  - Item 62: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.812 (1958:May 23). Item is in English.
  - Item 63: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.813 (1958:June 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 64: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.814 (1958:June 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 65: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.815 (1958:July 10). Item is in English.
  - Item 66: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.817 (1958:July 14). Item is in English.
  - Item 67: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.816 (1958:July 11). Item is in English.
  - Item 68: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.? (1958:Aug. 22). Item is in English.
  - Item 69: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.? (1958:Sep. 19). Item is in English.
  - Item 70: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.? (1958:Aug. 29). Item is in English.
  - Item 71: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.820 (1958:Aug. 8). Item is in English.
  - Item 72: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.? (1958:Oct. 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 73: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.? (1958:Oct. 10). Item is in English.
  - Item 74: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.? (1958:Oct. 31). Item is in English.
  - Item 75: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.? (1958:Nov. 21). Item is in English.
  - Item 76: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.831 (1958:Nov. 28). Item is in English.
  - Item 77: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.? (1958:Nov. 14). Item is in English.
  - Item 78: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)